megaproxy.com 2011-05-24

# Megaproxy.com, Inc \ Online privacy statement

Megaproxy.com, Inc ("Megaproxy") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. This policy applies only to Megaproxy, and not to the web sites of other companies or organizations visited using Megaproxy's service. Our privacy policy statement will help you understand Megaproxy's commitment to safeguarding your private information.

#### Information Collection and Use

Megaproxy does not collect any personal or individually identifiable information without the informed consent of the member. We will not sell, share, or rent your confidential information to third parties, including individuals or other organizations.

#### Server Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for performance accessments and aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Our servers automatically record the following information about each request to our site.

  * Request Protocol Type - HTTP/HTTPS
  * The requested URL
  * Your original and destination IP addresses
  * Size and Mime types of HTTP pages/transfers
  * Operating System type and Browser information
  * Referrer URL address and Domain Name
  * The date and time
  * Version of Encryption Algorithm supported by the Browser

The logging data above is collected as part of our attempt to monitor ongoing performance and service integrity in order to enhance our service offering. We have implemented strict technical and organizational measures to ensure that the log data is protected at all times and destroyed after statistical analysis by our security and performance engineering teams. Additional service performance statistics logs may be collected from time to time in order to evaluate the scalability of the Megaproxy service and/or introduce new service enhancements.

#### Intelligent Caching

Megaproxy uses extensive caching technology to cache frequently requested Web content. Caching mechanisms are used to serve web pages directly from the Megaproxy local storage as a means to make web performance faster and more efficient. We do not cache or locally store any end-to-end web content transfers, like e-commerce transactions, via the Secure Socket Layer (SSL).

#### Internet Cookies

Megaproxy.com, Inc may use a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer to maintain a session state. These short-lived cookies are not written to your hard drive and are removed when you close the browser. This means that not only are your web activities kept private, but also that your hard drive memory is not depleted. Our customizable user preferences feature uses a single cookie, which is stored on your local hard drive. This cookie is used for user customizable privacy options. Megaproxy does not, and will not, use cookies to retrieve personal information about you.

#### Sharing

We may share aggregate demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information and cannot identify any individual person.

#### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Megaproxy is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information for their protection. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Megaproxy web site.

#### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

#### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users information. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. Megaproxy.com, Inc is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have incorporated physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information. 

#### Notification of Changes

This privacy statement was last updated on June 24, 2004. A notice will be posted on this web page for 30 days whenever this privacy statement is changed. If you have further questions regarding our privacy practices, please send email inquiries to [PRIVACY HELP](mailto:support@megaproxy.com).
